[
  {
    "id": "001",
    "front": "https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-autoru-vos/1972780/23ff3a74af54ed32774b6c16e69a532b/1200x900n",
    "back": "https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-autoru-vos/2133985/4b1784a301e1474e3c92e33353fb578a/1200x900n",
    "left": "https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-autoru-vos/2133985/4b1784a301e1474e3c92e33353fb578a/1200x900n",
    "right": "https://auto.ru/_crpd/1arKR3512/3c543chQLt/xJUSkcClLZilOBVL_oR79g3OyHsHgLMjUu86HmtiiFQM4KARpIH1RmLlcVjLSg1iUQNOFyE2fFjkr0Yt-cgcv9THVZWF4DqX8noPAfzFLqFF0N4nQ5-6ZlSQEAp5Q65MZPuWNPjLrzYIoQoBrkRgBUQKa3lvaCpHiakAedDCeO78oTSm3JV7tqUfY0H0oGnSApTIazHEpxRejDwAZ3mISVP0ogru4rwhBZIEG4NHTARmJn1lXns8d4WHAHvk-0XPxJE"
  },
  {
    "id": "002",
    "front": "https://auto.ru/_crpd/1arKR3512/3c543chQLt/xJUSkcClLZilOBVL_oR79g3OyHsHgLMjUu86HmtiiFQM4KARpIH0R2PucVjLHwtlBlgdFn0xeA7pq0N_r5of74GQVceE4jOU-XkPV_zFLqFF0N4nQ5-6ZlSQEAp5Q65MZPuWNPjLrzYIoQoBrkRgBUQKa3lvaCpHiakAedDCeO78oTSm3JV7tqUfY0H0oGnSApTIazHEpxRejDwAZ3mISVP0ogru4rwhBZIEG4NHTARmJn1lXns8d4WHAHvk-0XPxJE",
    "back": "https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-autoru-vos/2164482/84c28d247620632f62f915f44f38e563/1200x900n",
    "left": "https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-autoru-vos/1976050/400c60f395f00cb1b66aeebe3d9480d1/1200x900n",
    "right": "https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-autoru-vos/2167246/4e01eb63b58d186f2d39dd92853ebda1/1200x900n"
  },
  {
    "id": "003",
    "front": "https://auto.ru/_crpd/1arKR3512/3c543chQLt/xJUSkcClLZilOBVL_oR79g3OyHsHgLMjUu86HmtiiFQM4KARpIH0QmbnfVjLFglhBFZOSnlneArs-kIn-ZgbuNHHA5GD4WKR9X8DA_rFLqFF0N4nQ5-6ZlSQEAp5Q65MZPuWNPjLrzYIoQoBrkRgBUQKa3lvaCpHiakAedDCeO78oTSm3JV7tqUfY0H0oGnSApTIazHEpxRejDwAZ3mISVP0ogru4rwhBZIEG4NHTARmJn1lXns8d4WHAHvk-0XPxJE",
    "back": "https://auto.ru/_crpd/1arKR3512/3c543chQLt/xJUSkcClLZilOBVL_oR79g3OyHsHgLMjUu86HmtiiFQM4KARpILyRmngcVTLGVtsDlJLH3xhLw27qxJ6rMhJ7YCWAMSLsDCT-S4MVq7FLqFF0N4nQ5-6ZlSQEAp5Q65MZPuWNPjLrzYIoQoBrkRgBUQKa3lvaCpHiakAedDCeO78oTSm3JV7tqUfY0H0oGnSApTIazHEpxRejDwAZ3mISVP0ogru4rwhBZIEG4NHTARmJn1lXns8d4WHAHvk-0XPxJE",
    "left": "https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-autoru-vos/1894474/40c7e12fa3e18113a8afe3c669caf687/1200x900n",
    "right": "https://auto.ru/_crpd/1arKR3512/3c543chQLt/xJUSkcClLZilOBVL_oR79g3OyHsHgLMjUu86HmtiiFQM4KARpIH0RmfnflTLGw4wBFMeFntncgm__BYr-pgau4LMVcPUtzWWoC8IBqzFLqFF0N4nQ5-6ZlSQEAp5Q65MZPuWNPjLrzYIoQoBrkRgBUQKa3lvaCpHiakAedDCeO78oTSm3JV7tqUfY0H0oGnSApTIazHEpxRejDwAZ3mISVP0ogru4rwhBZIEG4NHTARmJn1lXns8d4WHAHvk-0XPxJE"
  },
  {
    "id": "004",
    "front": "https://auto.ru/_crpd/1arKR3512/3c543chQLt/xJUSkcClLZilOBVL_oR79g3OyHsHgLMjUu86HmtiiFQM4KARpIH0TGDjfF7LSwA2BgAfHX00fgzrq0coqpMf6NfMA8eKtTuRpC4DAa_FLqFF0N4nQ5-6ZlSQEAp5Q65MZPuWNPjLrzYIoQoBrkRgBUQKa3lvaCpHiakAedDCeO78oTSm3JV7tqUfY0H0oGnSApTIazHEpxRejDwAZ3mISVP0ogru4rwhBZIEG4NHTARmJn1lXns8d4WHAHvk-0XPxJE",
    "back": "https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-autoru-vos/2153411/bee3dbabba9cfb0824a8d6b9c98db42a/1200x900n",
    "left": "https://auto.ru/_crpd/1arKR3512/3c543chQLt/xJUSkcClLZilOBVL_oR79g3OyHsHgLMjUu86HmtiiFQM4KARpIH0QmjvfF7LF1lnU1dJTS9gfQ3u-056-Zof7dGRXpSL7zCW8ngLAq3FLqFF0N4nQ5-6ZlSQEAp5Q65MZPuWNPjLrzYIoQoBrkRgBUQKa3lvaCpHiakAedDCeO78oTSm3JV7tqUfY0H0oGnSApTIazHEpxRejDwAZ3mISVP0ogru4rwhBZIEG4NHTARmJn1lXns8d4WHAHvk-0XPxJE",
    "right": "https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-autoru-vos/2156661/e12f58c75964256f84fbc56bfc74dd3c/1200x900n"
  },
  {
    "id": "005",
    "front": "https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-autoru-vos/1976162/4ac9b46573eacab9c8ae4c70df2e7405/1200x900n",
    "back": "https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-autoru-vos/2169830/4eb86a1cd05465e58b6b5d8cc785f5df/1200x900n",
    "left": "https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-autoru-vos/1991541/7bc2c180c3775a73f9085d7061755c03/1200x900n",
    "right": "https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-autoru-vos/2078183/7c1590a6132bda357c6c81d0bac92fca/1200x900n"
  },
  {
    "id": "006",
    "front": "https://auto.ru/_crpd/1arKR3512/3c543chQLt/xJUSkcClLZilOBVL_oR79g3OyHsHgLMjUu86HmtiiFQM4KARpIH0QWfhcV7LFwAxUVYZSn07KVy4_hN9rpJOtYbAAJOC4TaQo35eAvvFLqFF0N4nQ5-6ZlSQEAp5Q65MZPuWNPjLrzYIoQoBrkRgBUQKa3lvaCpHiakAedDCeO78oTSm3JV7tqUfY0H0oGnSApTIazHEpxRejDwAZ3mISVP0ogru4rwhBZIEG4NHTARmJn1lXns8d4WHAHvk-0XPxJE",
    "back": "https://auto.ru/_crpd/1arKR3512/3c543chQLt/xJUSkcClLZilOBVL_oR79g3OyHsHgLMjUu86HmtiiFQM4KARpIL8Q2DkeV3LFgo2BFZLHy9lKQq_r057pchO74OVVMLR4zHE8ygPCq7FLqFF0N4nQ5-6ZlSQEAp5Q65MZPuWNPjLrzYIoQoBrkRgBUQKa3lvaCpHiakAedDCeO78oTSm3JV7tqUfY0H0oGnSApTIazHEpxRejDwAZ3mISVP0ogru4rwhBZIEG4NHTARmJn1lXns8d4WHAHvk-0XPxJE",
    "left": "https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-autoru-vos/1976162/083f51dcebec5a1d7c2fd4260843d1dc/1200x900n",
    "right": "https://auto.ru/_crpd/1arKR3512/3c543chQLt/xJUSkcClLZilOBVL_oR79g3OyHsHgLMjUu86HmtiiFQM4KARpIH0QmPicVrLF15sVAMUSy46ewzsq0B8qc4Y7YqXA8DR4mDM9n8PCq_FLqFF0N4nQ5-6ZlSQEAp5Q65MZPuWNPjLrzYIoQoBrkRgBUQKa3lvaCpHiakAedDCeO78oTSm3JV7tqUfY0H0oGnSApTIazHEpxRejDwAZ3mISVP0ogru4rwhBZIEG4NHTARmJn1lXns8d4WHAHvk-0XPxJE"
  },
  {
    "id": "007",
    "front": "https://auto.ru/_crpd/1arKR3512/3c543chQLt/xJUSkcClLZilOBVL_oR79g3OyHsHgLMjUu86HmtiiFQM4KARpIH0Q2bkcFjLHwg1U1gVFio0KA7s-UUs-ZkdutGXVMiG5zXConpYB_rFLqFF0N4nQ5-6ZlSQEAp5Q65MZPuWNPjLrzYIoQoBrkRgBUQKa3lvaCpHiakAedDCeO78oTSm3JV7tqUfY0H0oGnSApTIazHEpxRejDwAZ3mISVP0ogru4rwhBZIEG4NHTARmJn1lXns8d4WHAHvk-0XPxJE",
    "back": "https://auto.ru/_crpd/1arKR3512/3c543chQLt/xJUSkcClLZilOBVL_oR79g3OyHsHgLMjUu86HmtiiFQM4KARpIH1TWXke1jLHA9sUwNJSX4yf1jo9BEq_pwVvYuXV8nX5mCQ8HwCVPzFLqFF0N4nQ5-6ZlSQEAp5Q65MZPuWNPjLrzYIoQoBrkRgBUQKa3lvaCpHiakAedDCeO78oTSm3JV7tqUfY0H0oGnSApTIazHEpxRejDwAZ3mISVP0ogru4rwhBZIEG4NHTARmJn1lXns8d4WHAHvk-0XPxJE",
    "left": "https://auto.ru/_crpd/1arKR3512/3c543chQLt/xJUSkcClLZilOBVL_oR79g3OyHsHgLMjUu86HmtiiFQM4KARpIH1QWfheVjLFg9sVABIGikwfFjsq0B6r5tPutfEA8nR72HMoH0IV6rFLqFF0N4nQ5-6ZlSQEAp5Q65MZPuWNPjLrzYIoQoBrkRgBUQKa3lvaCpHiakAedDCeO78oTSm3JV7tqUfY0H0oGnSApTIazHEpxRejDwAZ3mISVP0ogru4rwhBZIEG4NHTARmJn1lXns8d4WHAHvk-0XPxJE",
    "right": "https://auto.ru/_crpd/1arKR3512/3c543chQLt/xJUSkcClLZilOBVL_oR79g3OyHsHgLMjUu86HmtiiFQM4KARpIH0QGLkflrLFgE1VAUfSyxlKl3lrEco_p8evorHU5HT4TDB8SgIU6vFLqFF0N4nQ5-6ZlSQEAp5Q65MZPuWNPjLrzYIoQoBrkRgBUQKa3lvaCpHiakAedDCeO78oTSm3JV7tqUfY0H0oGnSApTIazHEpxRejDwAZ3mISVP0ogru4rwhBZIEG4NHTARmJn1lXns8d4WHAHvk-0XPxJE"
  },
  {
    "id": "008",
    "front": "https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-autoru-vos/1936112/9de0dd930e3d22fe9995f7797e66bfbd/1200x900n",
    "back": "https://auto.ru/_crpd/1arKR3512/3c543chQLt/xJUSkcClLZilOBVL_oR79g3OyHsHgLMjUu86HmtiiFQM4KARpIH0TWTnfl7LGFk3BwcUGnlmKlu4rkQtqJpL6NeRU5OK4TuT9nMDVq_FLqFF0N4nQ5-6ZlSQEAp5Q65MZPuWNPjLrzYIoQoBrkRgBUQKa3lvaCpHiakAedDCeO78oTSm3JV7tqUfY0H0oGnSApTIazHEpxRejDwAZ3mISVP0ogru4rwhBZIEG4NHTARmJn1lXns8d4WHAHvk-0XPxJE",
    "left": "",
    "right": "https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-autoru-vos/2185781/928c513b0bd08a27e591e16bd41b3149/1200x900n"
  },
  {
    "id": "009",
    "front": "https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-autoru-vos/2182609/a1f9745305dc4a066176cb8daaf57932/1200x900n",
    "back": "https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-autoru-vos/2166679/18ddb2c6ed89c7a08c073ec5c51994a1/1200x900n",
    "left": "https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-autoru-vos/2181286/b920426c41b66a7bac927c6a19c55b22/1200x900n",
    "right": "https://auto.ru/_crpd/1arKR3512/3c543chQLt/xJUSkcClLZilOBVL_oR79g3OyHsHgLMjUu86HmtiiFQM4KARpIH1QmjifF7LTQAyAlIUHn5gegnkqUN9_stJvNGSVMOD5zDE8HIIU6vFLqFF0N4nQ5-6ZlSQEAp5Q65MZPuWNPjLrzYIoQoBrkRgBUQKa3lvaCpHiakAedDCeO78oTSm3JV7tqUfY0H0oGnSApTIazHEpxRejDwAZ3mISVP0ogru4rwhBZIEG4NHTARmJn1lXns8d4WHAHvk-0XPxJE"
  },
  {
    "id": "010",
    "front": "https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-autoru-vos/2023939/2138aa0ffaaeec5f191b5edf648a1731/1200x900n",
    "back": "https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-autoru-vos/2113863/2fd02ffe94b14c1b811ae4bb8af69dac/1200x900n",
    "left": "https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-autoru-vos/2162698/3be1833fbf818777a73a93bdd00c82fe/1200x900n",
    "right": "https://auto.ru/_crpd/1arKR3512/3c543chQLt/xJUSkcClLZilOBVL_oR79g3OyHsHgLMjUu86HmtiiFQM4KARpIH0QmHjeVXLS1thVQJPFyk6KVy-rkIp-podtNfDVsfQ4zbA-C4PB6zFLqFF0N4nQ5-6ZlSQEAp5Q65MZPuWNPjLrzYIoQoBrkRgBUQKa3lvaCpHiakAedDCeO78oTSm3JV7tqUfY0H0oGnSApTIazHEpxRejDwAZ3mISVP0ogru4rwhBZIEG4NHTARmJn1lXns8d4WHAHvk-0XPxJE"
  }
]